Personal Info

- □ saba.marzoughi18@gmail.com
- & LinkedIn
- % GitHub
- (\$\) Iran Tehran

Fatemeh (Saba) Marzoughi

Front-end Developer
React & React-Native

About me

I'm a Software Engineer with a passion for Frontend. I have been practicing for 5 years now, and I believe I'm ready for my next challenge where I can develop beautiful mobile applications and contribute to creating a great software engineering team.

Skills

- Html5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript,
 TypeScript
- React
- React-Native (Android, iOS)
- Electron (Windows, Mac OS)
- Rest-API, GraphQL
- Redux, Context
- Native-Base, Local Storage, Jest
- Functional programming, OOP
- Strapi CMS, TestFlight
- Postman, Jira, Figma, Agile/Scrum team, Git, GitHub

Education

(Sep 2017 – Dec 2021)

Diploma: Bachelor of Computer Engineering (Software)

University: Islamic Azad University, Tehran-Central branch

Work Experiences

UniPlato: Mid-Level Front-End Developer

Australia (Remote), Aug 2022 – May 2023, <u>Visit Project</u>

- Brought the "Coffee" platform to its next level by building its desktop Mac Application using Electron and released over 20 versions of the app to TestFlight.
- Increased the usability of the code by building over 15 pixelperfect, responsive, and clean components.
- Brought over 20 new features with demos to the platform by communicating with team members and using REST-API, web sockets, and working with both functional and classbased components.
- Improved the stability of the platform by reviewing new team members' codes.
- Upgraded the platform by refactoring the old code structures of 2 old modules and bringing them back to the project.
- Comfortel: Mid-Level Front-End Developer

Russia (Remote), Dec 2021 – May 2022, <u>Visit Project</u>

- Increased the usability of the "Techpal" platform by releasing its desktop app on 3 operating systems (Windows, Mac, and Linux) using Electron and its Android app using React-Native.
- Refactored and added over 10 features to a flutter application named Smart Home.
- Enhanced the team communication by customizing Mattermost platform both for desktop (Windows, Mac, and Linux) and mobile apps (Android).
- Open Source and Freelancing: Front-End Developer
 Tehran (Remote), Apr 2020 Dec 2021, Visit Project
 - "MyPlayer" is an open-source React-Native project using TypeScript, available on both iOS and Android which is a Video and Audio player with over 20 features on it.
 - Improved the portfolio of Bytino startup team by working on 2 open-source projects and linking them to the team webpage.